# FRANCISCO PEREIRA

Degree in Informatics Engineering



Portugal

+351 926 843 295

@ franciscoandre.farp@gmail.com

My Portfolio in ffarps.github.io

in My linkedin

#### **OBJECTIVE**

My name is Francisco André Rodrigues Pereira, I'm 21 years old, from Mirandela, and I graduated from the Polytechnic Institute of Bragança with a degree in Informatics Engineering.

During the third year of the course and after completing it, I was awarded two research grants by the Centre for Research in Digitalisation and Intelligent Robotics (CeDRI).

Proactive and dedicated, ready to achieve great things.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Out 2023-now Personal Projects Development

Developing personal projects related to areas, frameworks and tools in which I want to invest some time and upgrading my technical know-how, my current goal is to apply the theoretical knowledge which I learned during my degree in these projects.

My web Portfolio in https://ffarps.github.io

Jul 2023-Sep 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Contributed to an OpenZDM project related to developing a C# and OpenGl-based tool in Unity 3D, that aims to reduce defects in production chains in a car factory in the assembly and *body shop* zones.

Jul 2022-Jan 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Worked on developing Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) apps in Unity, using different frameworks and tools, such as MRTK, ARCore, Vuforia SDK and ARFoundation.

## **EDUCATION**

Oct 2019-Jul 2023 Degree in Informatics Engineering

Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Mathematics, Information Systems.

Worked on many projects related to Web Development, Computer Architecture, Networking, 3D Modeling, Machine Learning, Data Structures, SQL and IoT.

2016-2019 High School Diploma

Science and technology

Agrupamento de Escolas de Mirandela

## LANGUAGES

Portuguese - native English - proficient

# HARD SKILLS

- C#, Python, Java, TypeScript, JavaScript, Rust, etc
- Git
- Linux
- · Unity 3D
- · SQL
- · Cloud

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- · Self-taught
- · Attention to detail
- Technical Writing
- Teamwork